No kidding.
A big freakin' gator stuffed
with 20 keys of H on the roof.
Now. we're driving up
some dirt road.
car's bobbing around.
I'm hanging out...
hanging on to the tail
trying to keep this thing
from falling off...
-Come on.
-Trying to make the drop.
Meantime. my cousin
is screaming.
they will make kill of us.
This guy...
the second he gets scared.
he forgets his English.
Luka. you... you're insane.
-I'm fun.
-It's different.
See. I think we established
I'm the fun one.
-I know.
-You are.
That's why I'm glad
we reconnected. blondie.
Me too.
My dude.
-She's fine.
-I think Luka Simovic agrees.
Can you focus?
We're trying to take down
a major narco family.
I am just more worried
about Scola's family.
Look. Nina worked Luka
back in the day as a UC
on a fugitive task force. okay?
The guy's a beta.
She's got him
wrapped around her finger.
I'll be right back.
-Mm-hmm.
-Okay.
Okay. the meet is gonna be
in 20 minutes.
Nina. he's coming back.
-Hi.
Sorry.
-Yeah.
-Just got to...
Uh. listen. I. um... uh...
I got a work thing
I got to attend to.
-Oh.
-Um...
Are you trying to reach
your sales target?
Always.
How about. uh.
I go handle business.
and. uh. we meet back
at my place later for a drink?
I have other refreshments. too.
Oh. your place. huh?
-I feel like I barely know you.
-What you talking about?
We used to party
before you split for Miami.
Wait. Wait. wait. wait. what
if I want to watch you work?
Ashley. girl.
are you testing me?
Always. Come on. listen.
we can roll together.
And then I can make sure you're
not just talking a big game.
I'm not just talking.
You're with a player right now.
Prove it.
Or I can go home and curl up
with a good book.
Wow.
Come on.
Ashley is fun.
Okay. this is good.
This is what we were aiming for.
Nina talked herself
into the big show.
putting us one step closer
to our goal.
which you will remember
is to document Luka Simovic
moving felony amounts of heroin
and then flipping him
against his father. Drago.
czar of the Simovic clan.
And if you haven't heard.
there is chatter
that he is about
to flood the tri-state area
with black tar heroin.
But you know what?
I don't think we're gonna
let him do that. do you?
-Jubal.
-Yeah.
SWAT wants a meet location.
Uh. uh. oh. yeah?
Well. we can't give 'em
what we don't have.
Hey. SWAT.
you'll know it when we do.
Our agents
are tailing Luka's car.
When he lands at the location.
they'll get into position
to record the deal.
Ta-da.
-Money?
-I thought you moved weight.
Tonight
I'm picking up a present.
Stay here.
This guy. he...
he don't like surprises.
Be right back.
-Jubal. heads up...
-our intel was wrong.
Luka isn't dealing tonight.
He's buying.
Well. either way.
we arrest him transacting.
and it's leverage.
Jubal. we don't
have a line of sight.
and there's no way we can roll
this van in there
without being seen.
Well. the JOC doesn't have
any cams in that lot either.
so we have no eyes up.
which means
we cannot record
the deal. people.
Okay. so we pivot... we pull
Luka over on the way home
and arrest him for possession
with intent.
No. I didn't spend
the last two months
getting close to this guy
to not catch him in the act.
We have no choice with no
cams on the surveillance van.
We don't need 'em.
I'm gonna record him
on my button cam.
-No. Nina. do not do that.
-It's too risky.
Be prepared to move in.
-Scola. it's fine. She's got...
-OA. please!
Luka.
Aren't you gonna introduce me
to your friend?
Hey. I told you to come alone.
-Whoa. whoa. relax.
-She's just a good time.
-Hi.
-I'm Ashley.
-See what I mean?
-Now. let's get this done.
Yours ain't the only deal
I want to close tonight.
Whoo!
Big boy.
That's what I'm talking about.
-This what you're looking for?
-I got to admit...
I didn't think you'd actually
be able to find it.
Good. 'cause the price
just went up.
What just happened?
Luka's connect
just changed the terms.
-What the hell. bro?
-We had a deal.
You need it today.
Rush delivery
means premium pricing.
40 more.
Luka. Hey.
We didn't come all this way
to not close the deal. right?
I mean. if we did. I...
No. no. no.
This...
this was my old man's
Royal Oak. okay?
That should cover your 40
and then some.
-We good?
-Yeah. we're good.
Please just get a look at
the drugs and get out of there.
Okay. you made me an accomplice.
-Show me what we bought.
-Oh. you're curious?
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
-Mm-hmm.
-Are you ready?
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Who the hell is that?
Jubal. someone
just crashed our meet.
-Did SWAT jump the gun?
-No. negative! It's not us!
Hey! Back! Get back!
Someone's ripping off the deal.
Luka! It's not worth
risking your life.
Let's go!
If I go back to my dad
empty-handed.
-I won't have a life.
-Hey.
Get the money.
Come on! Come on!
-Give me this.
-Hey. hey. hey. go!
Where did you put it?
We got to get out of here.
Ashley. we got to go.
Yeah. fun's over.
You're under arrest.
So a rip crew just swooped in
and murdered
Luka Simovic's supplier
and then made off
with the score.
And they also fired
on an undercover federal agent.
And while that last part
really gets my goat.
uh. the missing contraband
is really the issue at hand.
We have an APB
for a black BMW X6 out now.
All right. folks.
are we any closer
to figuring out
who hijacked our sting
and made off with that case?
Uh. about that case.
I don't think Luka
was buying heroin tonight.
Fingerprints taken
at the scene of the crime
ID the man Luka was meeting
as Graham Renner. 45.
He wasn't a dealer.
He was a fence.
So Luka Simovic
could've been buying anything.
from stolen goods...
Yeah. to a... to a partridge
in a pear tree.
Yeah. except our goal was to
flip Luka to get to his father.
If he was buying a partridge.
there's nothing illegal
about that.
And now we have nothing
to flip him with.
-Right.
-Well. we got six hours
before we have to put this guy
in front of a judge or kick him.
I guess we should use
what little leverage we have
to see if we can get him to
tell us what was in that case.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
All right.
Well. that was some mess
back there. huh?
Yeah. well. it was my job
to work Luka for intel.
Now we got one dead
and no leads?
I should be in there. okay?
I mean. I know him better than
anybody after these few months.
I know his insecurities.
I can get him to talk.
Honey. don't take this
the wrong way.
but I think that
you're the last person
that he's gonna talk to
right now.
Besides. I think we've taken on
enough risk for one night.
don't you?
Okay. would you say
that to any other agent?
Are you any other agent. Nina?
Or are you
the mother of our child?
Hmm.
Where's Ashley?
I'd like to give her
a piece of my mind.
Why don't you start by
answering our questions first?
-What was in the case. Luka?
-Vintage porno mags.
-Oh. that's really funny.
-Yeah. I thought so.
You know. the faster you
talk. the sweeter the deal.
I'm not gonna do
your job for you.
-Okay? It's embarrassing.
-Well. you would know.
Oh. what's that
supposed to mean?
You're a grown man still
taking orders from your dad.
Don't forget about his brother.
-Oh. yeah. right.
-He's a capo now.
Aren't you older than him?
That's got to sting
a little bit.
taking orders
from your little brother.
Everybody knows
your dad thinks you're a joke.
What's he gonna say
when he finds out
you walked a Fed right
into the middle of a deal?
We're gonna find out
what you bought.
This is your only chance
to help yourself.
Charge me or don't.
I'm not saying another word.
All right.
so Luka's not talking.
So how do we find this crew
that scooped this deal?
Is there anyone out
there celebrating
a big score tonight?
NYPD. I'm looking at you.
No?
Well. whoever
was behind this rip
had to know when and where
it was taking place.
Maybe a leak
on Luka's side of the deal?
Okay. just finished
dumping Luka's phone.
Seems before
contacting the fence.
he reached out
to a local Brazilian crew
about procuring
something special.
Right. right.
so he calls around.
says he has 300K to pony up
for a present...
And unwittingly tips off
this Brazilian crew
of a lucrative deal
about to go down.
Right. I mean.
it's as good a theory as any.
-Maybe more than a theory.
-Hmm?
I'm looking at security footage
from outside the bar
where Luka and Nina were at.
Check out what's parked
across the street.
Oh. black BMW X6.
-Can we run that plate?
-On it.
Yeah. registered
to a José Santos in Astoria.
Whoa. José is a known
associate of Trem Bala...
bad. bad guys.
Get a team to Astoria.
-Okay.
-Three. two. one.
FBI. Show me your hands.
Show me your hands.
Hey.
Hey. hey.
Hey!
Show me your hands.
Put it down. nice and easy.
That's it.
Get out.
Maggie. I found
what's in the case.
You need to see this.
Is that what I think it is?
Is that a rocket launcher?
An M-95 Stinger.
No wonder you didn't
want to talk. Luka.
You're a terrorist.
You bought
a Stinger missile system.
That's a violation
of 18 U.S. code 2332G...
the unlawful purchase
of a missile
designed to take down
an aircraft.
That is 25 years
before upgrades.
What are you doing
with a missile?
Unless it's for your dad.
Well. that would make sense...
why you haven't contacted
your family lawyer.
Are you trying to get off the
hook without him finding out?
You don't know my family.
Luka. we're booking you.
Your face is gonna be
all over the news.
Your dad's gonna see it.
You're finished.
You want me to roll on my dad?
Fine.
Hell. I'll even do you
one better.
But I need assurances first...
witness protection.
We could talk to the AUSA.
if you start talking right now.
What does your dad want
with a Stinger?
You know what happened
to the Jalisco Cartel?
Of course.
Federales took out
their top boss. Jorge Ortega.
and their whole C-suite
when they shot their plane
out of the air last month.
all thanks to an anonymous tip.
What if I told you
the Stinger's a gift
for the new boss?
The DEA has no record
of the cartel
appointing a new boss.
No. you've been warring
with that family for a decade.
Why would you be giving them
a present now?
'Cause it's rude to show up
to a wedding without a gift.
It's a merger.
My family and Jalisco.
united in holy matrimony.
My little bro Nikola
is marrying
Jorge Ortega's daughter.
And to mark the occasion.
my dad and Jalisco
are negotiating a deal.
They front us $500 million
worth of product.
we double their money.
So the missile
is a symbolic gesture
in case the cartel
wants to pay back
the Mexican government
for killing their leadership.
My family's way
of showing solidarity.
Luka says the wedding
is happening this afternoon
at his father's estate
in Orient Point.
Oh. okay. Did Luka ID
the new leader of Jalisco?
No. he says he has no idea.
Claims his father. Drago.
has been dealing
with them directly.
-Right.
-Well. the JOC's digging in.
But whoever the new leader is.
a merger between
these two families...
-Would be disastrous.
-Yeah.
All right. folks. so we know
the what. where. and why
of this criminal merger.
but we still need the who.
so where are we
with identifying
the new Jalisco boss?
Former leader was Jorge Ortega.
but it can't be any
of his known capos.
They were all killed last month
when Federales
shot their plane down.
With a Stinger missile. right?
Luckily. we've got SIGINT.
DEA wiretaps
of the Ortega family
suggest the new leader is
Carlos Ortega. Jorge's brother.
All right.
Lives in Madrid.
been a fringe presence
in the cartel up till now.
Okay. so little bro's
first act as new cartel leader
was to broker a ceasefire
with the Simovic clan
by marrying off his niece.
Yeah. followed by negotiating
one of the biggest
narcotics deals in history.
Right. so all we have to do
to stop it is figure out a way
to infiltrate one of New York's
most heavily guarded estates
and record the deal between
these two criminal enterprises.
So. according to Luka.
we're gonna be entering
through this corridor down here.
but the event is gonna be held
in this room.
So what makes you think Luka
isn't gonna double-cross you
the second he walks the two
of you into this wedding?
-It's gonna work. all right?
-Trust me.
-Oh. I trust you. completely.
-Are you sure?
Because you're acting
like I haven't already
considered the risks.
Yeah. I was just hoping maybe
we could consider them together
before you decide to volunteer
to storm Omaha Beach.
You don't really sound
like an agent right now.
No? What do I sound like
right now. then?
Like an overbearing husband.
Well. we both know
that that's not the case.
seeing as how
we're not married. okay?
Look. I'm not gonna apologize
for holding you to a deal
that we made.
We have an agreement.
One of us
takes a high-risk case.
the other one takes the bench
so...
our son doesn't risk
losing both of us.
Yeah. you're right.
So go home.
Uh...
Uh. so the Stinger missile
for Jalisco. it's a gift?
Yeah. which is why Luka can't
go to the party empty-handed.
But we're obviously not gonna
give him a weapon of war.
-Great.
-That's why I deactivate it.
Now officially the world's
most expensive paperweight.
But I'm also gonna install
this audio transmitter
magnetically sealed
under the launcher.
And what if they have
an RF blocker?
-Good question.
-Thought about that.
This device. it can be switched
from transmit to local record
if needed.
Okay. so all we have
to do is make sure
that that case
gets into the room
where Drago and Carlos's deal
is going down.
That's right.
As long as this thing
is in range.
-JOC will get everything.
-Okay.
And when we get audio
and visual confirmation.
we'll come in with SWAT.
take down both organizations.
-Sounds good.
-Works for me.
Scola?
Sounds good.
Okay. we have got you five-by
on audio and visual.
This plan could go sideways
100 different ways.
-but I'm here with you. man.
-Thanks. dude.
Look. I'm sorry about snapping
at you last night
in the van. okay?
It was not okay.
Don't worry about it. man.
Thanks.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I mean. we did it
to ourselves. right?
What do they always say?
Well. never date
a fellow agent. for starters.
That's the one.
Luka. who are these girls?
They're FBI.
The look on his face!
Ooh. ooh.
Relax.
It's a party. bro.
And you are standing
in my house.
I bring in who I want
and what I want.
Now. please. Bogdan...
show my guests some respect.
Apologies. ladies.
But all guests
must turn in their phones.
Gentlemen. over there. with me.
Luka?
Mm.
Oh.
What kind of game
are you trying to run here?
I got you in. didn't I?
Well. just remember...
you only get a deal
if we make it out alive.
With what we came for.
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
Look happy.
I don't see Carlos Ortega.
Maybe he's not here yet.
If he was. you'd know it.
All right. so my dad does all
his deals in the smoking room.
So. if it's okay...
I'm gonna go place the gift now?
Then you come right back.
No funny business... otherwise.
you can kiss WITSEC goodbye.
You already got me
by the balls. blondie.
No need to keep squeezing.
-Hmm.
-Have fun.
Hmm.
Okay. OA. we're inside.
No sign of Carlos Ortega yet.
There's more wedding guests
than we anticipated...
40. maybe 50.
Maggie.
-Repeat. Maggie.
-Repeat.
OA?
-Nina. can you hear me?
-What the hell is happening?
-Must be a signal jammer.
-Jubal. we lost eyes and ears.
-Same on our end.
-We're completely blind.
For now. Maggie and Nina
are on their own.
All right. folks.
we have two agents adrift
and a jammer blocking all comms.
So what is our plan
to get back on track?
Can we tap into the estate's
security-camera system?
Will be tricky. but we can try.
Jubal. this is not safe.
We need to pull them
out of there now.
No. we cannot risk
walking into a buzz saw.
Then we extract them quietly.
These are two violent cartels
on high alert.
They hear our footsteps. this
is gonna turn into a bloodbath.
Okay. so you want us to just
sit in here on our hands.
Is that it. Jubal?
That's not
what we're doing. Scola.
We're gonna locate the jammer.
restore communication.
For now. you need to await
further instructions.
If our comms are down.
that means the bug inside
the case is jammed up. too.
so we can't record the deed.
-No. No. no. no.
-There's the local record mode.
All I need to do is...
Hey. the gift is in place.
The plans have changed.
Your family
is scrambling our comms.
I need to get back in there
and switch it over.
Are you trying to get us killed?
Your freedom depends on it.
Okay down the hall.
third room on your left.
Thank you.
Ortega could arrive any second.
-How we doing?
-Geolocation tools confirm
jammer is somewhere
on the property.
but I cannot disarm it
from here.
Okay. so OA and Scola
are gonna to do it manually.
Basically. yes.
Which means they
have to infiltrate
the estate in broad daylight.
And before you
say "basically. yes."
you're telling me
they have to search
every square inch
of the property?
Basical... Uh. no. there is
a spectrum detector on the van.
picks up the frequency
of local signals.
-should make it somewhat easier.
-Okay. great.
As long as
they don't get caught.
Ian. the spectrum detector
is showing the strongest signal
on the east side
of the building.
Copy. Keep sweeping
in that direction.
Scola. on your left.
Okay. you're clear.
Let's move.
Luka.
Tata.
You brought guests?
Today of all days?
I. uh. thought
we were celebrating.
Ashley.
It doesn't matter
what you think.
Our guests won't like it.
But they will like their gift.
which I delivered
just like I promised.
You proud?
Jubal. we're approaching
the east side
of the property now.
What the hell's that sound?
Uh. that would be the chopper
landing on the lawn.
This has got to be Ortega.
All right. yeah. let me see
if I can get you guys a visual.
Okay. I got Scola's feed up.
All right. let's see
if we can identify
these party guests
arriving fashionably late.
-Is that...
-I'll link facial rec.
Confirm...
that is Carlos Ortega. 54.
brother of the late
Jorge Ortega.
So DEA's SIGINT was right.
Carlos is the new head
of the cartel.
-All right. ho... hold on.
-Can you freeze it right there?
Right.
Who's the lady?
That is Jorge's widow.
Alicia Ortega. 45...
-mother of the bride.
-All right. can we...
can we track where
the helicopter took off from?
Uh. yeah. cross-referencing
the tail number
with its flight plan.
Looks like
they spoofed ADS-B flight data.
so best guess is
it took off from a yacht
somewhere
in international waters.
Right.
That explains how they got
into the country undetected.
Yeah. they brought some muscle.
Isobel. this
is looking kind of dicey.
Should we move in now?
Negative. Carlos Ortega
hasn't broken any laws.
And if we want to take down
this cartel for good.
we need more than him
entering the country illegally.
Copy.
Ian. keep trying
to find that jammer.
We've got to get eyes and ears
up inside the estate.
If we can tie Carlos
to this impending deal
with the Simovic family. we can
take down the Jalisco Cartel
and the Simovics
once and for all.
-Yeah. you heard the boss.
-Keep looking.
We got two big fish on the line.
Let's not lose either.
Yo.
What are you doing in here?
I was just looking
for the bathroom.
Bathroom's on
the opposite end of the hall.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
I knew you'd be a problem.
What's taking her so long?
Maggie knows
what she's doing. okay?
She's gonna get us all killed.
-Hey.
-You need to take a breath.
Or maybe you're
not worried enough.
-No.
-Hey. hey. you are spinning out.
Let's calm down. okay?
Well. that's definitely Carlos.
Thanks for coming.
Carlos. welcome.
Thank you
for coming all this way.
And miss my niece's wedding?
What a beautiful day.
You know Alicia...
my brother's widow
and mother of the bride.
Of course.
I'm sorry for your loss.
But I think we can agree
your husband would consider
today a cause for celebration.
I'm certain he would.
Given the history
between our organizations.
I-I never thought
a day like this
would be possible...
my Nikola marrying your Rosa.
Perhaps we can move on
to other matters in private.
Actually. before we go further.
we'd like to inspect the room
where we'll be conducting
our business today.
Certainly.
Luka...
take them to the smoking room.
Let's go.
How was the flight in. guys?
Got a helicopter on the lawn...
pretty sick.
So. anyways.
is this place killer?
Built in. I want to say. 1903.
Clearly. the guy
spared no expense.
Oh. and you got to check out
the gardens.
-They are absolutely insane.
-Leave us.
Yeah. sure.
Yeah. I'll just...
I'm having second thoughts.
Check that room first.
Jubal. I got eyes on Nina.
Looks like
she's still operational.
-Okay. great.
-What about Maggie?
Uh. negative.
I don't know.
I don't know if this is what
my brother would've wanted.
You are pathetic.
This is why
he left me in charge.
You never had the spine
to do what needs to be done.
After today. everybody's
gonna fear us again.
-I meant no offense.
-Like I said. pathetic.
And this room is way too small.
I need every Simovic present.
not just their capos.
They're expecting
a traditional intimate...
-The main room is nice.
-We'll end it there.
Oh. Luka.
-Luka.
-Hi.
-Hi. hi.
-What's going on in here?
The Ortegas think
the smoking room's too small
for the meet.
so we're moving it.
They...
Want everybody to hear.
That doesn't make any sense.
The meeting was
only supposed to be
for the heads of the family so
that they could seal the deal.
Why the change?
Why do they want everyone
in the same room?
I-I don't know.
They don't tell me
this kind of stuff.
Maggie.
Alicia is the new head
of the cartel. not Carlos.
Something is about to go down.
-I got a bad feeling about this.
-What?
-I think we call it.
-We got to get out of here.
Yeah. let's go.
Excuse me. we need to get out.
-No.
-No one leaves.
-They've blocked both exits.
-Mm-hmm.
If they wanted to kill us all...
We're like fish in a barrel.
-Jubal.
-Yeah. talk to me.
I've isolated the jammer.
The signal origin's
somewhere in this area.
That's... that looks
like a guardhouse. right?
Could be
in a security control room.
-Yeah.
-OA. Scola. listen up.
There's a guardhouse in
the east corner of the estate.
We think the jammer is in there.
likely along with multiple
Simovic guards.
so take caution.
-Copy.
-We'll take it out.
Jubal. we're approaching
the guardhouse.
Guys?
Jubal. do you copy?
Guys can you hear me?
They're jamming us now.
This has got to be it.
These guys are Jalisco.
So. if these are cartel muscle.
what the hell
were they doing in there?
Dead.
OA. it's a double cross.
Jalisco Cartel is not here
for a merger.
This is a takeover.
Found the jammer.
Jubal. the jammer's down.
Can you hear us?
All right. folks. we're back
and not a second to spare.
Maggie. Nina. we're back.
Can you hear me?
-Jubal...
-Wait.
-Something has changed.
-Yeah.
All the families are gathered
inside the great room.
What the hell's going on
down there?
Drago Simovic's security team
has been taken down.
The Ortegas are making a play.
-This was never a wedding.
-This was a massacre.
Maggie. Nina. did you copy that?
You need to get out there.
We're in the main room
trapped with no exit.
Before we chart
our futures together. a gift.
Let's split up.
All right.
Same make and model
those savages used
to shoot your husband's plane
out of the sky.
Now revenge can be yours.
if you choose to seek it.
In fact. I do plan
to seek it. imminently.
Now our gift to you.
What is this. a joke?
You recognize him. don't you?
It's Alonso Vega.
my husband's driver.
the rat who snitch on my family
and told the Federales
which plane he was flying.
I figure you might want it.
seeing as how you pay him
to betray us.
Oh. you stupid woman.
You would throw away everything?
My husband was everything.
To be clear.
I have no intention
of throwing away this union.
But we have new terms.
My family's now in control
of your entire operation.
You all report to me now.
Understood?
Of course. there are still
some redundancies.
-No. no. no. no.
-No. don't shoot me.
Shoot her.
She's FBI.
-Change of plans...
-kill them all!
Hey!
Nina. meet me at the exit.
-Nina!
-Scola.
She went after Alicia...
east wing.
OA. come with me.
Come on. go.
No. no. no. no.
-Oh. my God.
Oh.
Great shot.
Thank you. Thank you.
-You're under arrest.
-No. we had a deal.
-Deal's off the table.
-You outed us.
Turn around.
-Nina. Scola. can you hear me?
-The chopper is spooling up.
If Alicia makes it on board.
we will never find her!
Today is a great day
for New York.
Thanks to the heroic efforts
of our FBI field agents.
leadership of two major
criminal enterprises...
the Simovic clan
and the Jalisco Cartel...
have been completely dismantled
as part of Operation Confetti.
crippling heroin trade
for years to come.
-Okay. let's get out of here?
-Yeah.
Hey. It was nice
riding with you.
Next time we won't wear heels.
Yeah. See ya.
Bye.
Well...
that was a tough one.
Yeah.
Yeah. it was.
I. uh...
I put you in a tight spot.
I'm sorry.
I-I was in the wrong.
You know.
I-I think I just forgot
what that side of you
looked like.
What side?
It's the side that. um...
like. edges up to the line
and then just completely blasts
right over it.
Yeah.
Yep.
And it's the side
that I fell in love with.
Yeah.
Stakes have changed. right?
You know. today was
the first day...
I thought. I'm not...
I'm not making it
out of this one.
And I thought
about you and Dougie
and how through all
of the pain and grief.
you'd be sitting
in some courtroom somewhere
just dealing with our affairs.
I don't... I don't ever
want to do that to you. okay?
What are you saying?
Stuart Scola...
what I'm saying
is that after everything
we have been through.
-will you...
-Wait. Hold on.
Don't... don't say it.
Don't talk.
One second.
No.
-Uh...
-Don't... don't...
I'm in the middle
of asking you something.
-Yeah.
-Just... uh. I know...
-Ah. Okay. Here it is.
-Mm.
I've been holding on to this
thing for. like. six months.
Okay. Yes. 'cause you
couldn't just let me ask you.
No. okay?
We got to do one thing...
the normal way.
-One.
-Yeah.
Okay.
So will you marry me or what?
♪ All inside
♪ Our Amsterdam.
she hides ♪
♪ Watery eyes ♪
♪ That howling wind.
she's waving hi ♪
♪ Her other hand's in mine ♪
♪ Oh. and churches
and trains ♪
♪ Well. they all look
the same to me now ♪
♪ They shoot you some place ♪
♪ While we ache
to come home somehow ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm